By the decision of Ying Zheng, the king that wished to unite all of China,
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）
天下統一の道を行く王 嬴政(えいせい)のもと
the State of Qin began its invasion of the State of Wei.
秦国(しんこく)は 魏国(ぎこく)へと侵攻した
The enemy blocking their way is the legendary Great General, Lian Po.
立ちはだかる敵は
伝説の大将軍 廉頗(れんぱ)
Young generals take on this relentless battlefield in hopes of rendering great military achievements.
若き将たちは 大いなる武功を狙い
この苛烈な戦場に挑む
Tomorrow, we have the Yuehua Unit, the Yufeng Unit, and the Feixin Unit attack in a group
（蒙恬(もうてん)）
明日 楽華(がくか)隊 玉鳳(ぎょくほう)隊 飛信(ひしん)隊の―
３隊で打って出て
輪虎(りんこ)を討ち取ろう
and take down Lun Hu!
Okay, then I'll tell it to you.
（蒙恬）じゃ 作戦を言おう
First, the Yuehua Unit will target Lun Hu's headquarters on our own.
まずは
楽華隊が単独で輪虎の本陣を目指す
Now!
今だ！
What?!
（輪虎）なに？
For the first stage of the plan...
（蒙恬）作戦の第１段階
the Yuehua Unit will not target Lun Hu.
楽華隊は輪虎を狙わない
United Front of Three Units
They divided a mere 800 soldiers into five groups?
僅か800の兵を 更に５つに割った
Just what is this force supposed to do against my headquarters of 5,000?
（輪虎）
5,000からなる この本陣に対し―
それに何の意味がある？
よし！ 入るぞ！
Okay, we're heading in!
そして 普通に入ってくるのか
And they're just going to come in normally?
That's not clever, it's just eccentric.
それじゃ
奇策じゃなくて 奇行でしょう
You're just going to die pointlessly.
ただムダに死ぬだけだよ
Lord Meng Ao! The young lord...!
（郭叫(かくきょう)）蒙驁(もうごう)さま 若君が…
楽華隊が単独で敵本陣に…
The Yuehua Unit is attacking the enemy headquarters alone!
（蒙驁）うむ…
（蒙驁）蒙恬… 一体 何を…
Meng Tian...
Just what are you thinking?
（郭叫）すぐに呼び戻せ！
（伝令）ははっ！
We must call them back immediately!
Yes, sir!
No, wait.
（蒙驁）いや 待て
（伝令）はぁ？
Sir?
Father, about Meng Tian,
（蒙武(もうぶ)）親父(おやじ)どの 蒙恬のことだが
is he still halted as a 300-Man General?
（蒙武）
まだ三百人将にとどめているのか？
過保護は成長を妨げるぞ
Being overprotective will hinder his growth.
（蒙驁）
お前は ほったらかしすぎなのじゃ
You're too negligent.
You should have a bit more faith in him.
もう少し あいつを信用してやれ
（蒙驁）うん？
（蒙武）なよついたガキだが
He may be a bit of a gentle child,
あいつは そこらの千人将より
はるかに ものが見えている
but he's far more perceptive than most of the Thousand-Man Generals around here.
それは親父どのが
いちばん分かってるはずだ
You know that better than anyone, Father.
Trust in Meng Tian.
（蒙武）蒙恬を信じてやれ
If he dies, that means that's all of a man he was.
死んだら 死んだで
それまでの男だったということだ
Meng Tian...
（蒙驁）蒙恬…
Grandpa, check it out! A crab!
（蒙恬）
じいちゃん 見て！ ほら カニ！
うむ…
（蒙驁）
土門(どもん)将軍に伝令じゃ
Send this message to General Tu Men.
Yes, sir!
（蒙驁）
〝楽華隊は独立遊軍〞
The Yuehua Unit is an independent unit. Allow them act on their own discretion.
〝このまま自由に
やらせるように〞と
（郭叫）
ハッ… し… しかし…
B-But sir!
（蒙驁）行け！
（伝令）は… ははっ！
Go!
Yes, sir!
I know, Meng Tian.
（蒙驁）分かっておるよ 蒙恬
I know you're the most talented of these three generations of the Meng family...
お前が 我ら蒙家三代で
最も才能があることは
But...
じゃが…
I absolutely cannot allow you to die pointlessly!
（蒙驁）
無駄死にだけはするでないぞ
The enemy has invaded us unexpectedly!
（輪虎兵）敵は
思いのほか侵入してきています！
What's going on here?!
（圭）どういうことだ？
（輪虎）守備の継ぎ目を
狙ってくるからでしょう
They're probably targeting the joining points of the defense.
If that's their plan, it sure is a shallow one.
それが策だっていうんなら
やっぱり浅はかだなぁ
Cause of course, in those areas...
（輪虎）
そういう所には ちゃんと…
I've made sure to place my own veteran soldiers.
（輪虎）百戦錬磨の僕の兵が
配置してあるから
Lord Meng Tian!
（兵士）蒙恬さま！
（蒙恬）ああ
Yeah!
There you are, Lun Hu soldiers!
出たな 輪虎兵
（楚水(そすい)）ここは
歩兵に任せて問題なさそうです
It doesn't look like there will be any problem leaving this area to the foot soldiers.
騎馬隊は
いつでも出られます 信(しん)どの
The mounted unit can leave any time, Lord Xin!
（楚水）信どの…
（信）ンンッ…
Lord Xin...
Wha-?!
You're not gonna go after Lun Hu?!
（信）輪虎を狙わないって？
What do you mean, Meng Tian?!
どういうことだ？ 蒙恬
Tomorrow, the Yuehua Unit will target...
明日 楽華隊が狙うのは…
Lun Hu's soldiers.
輪虎兵だ
The Lun Hu soldiers? You're saying you're going after his men?!
輪虎兵？
兵隊を狙うって言ってんのか？
（蒙恬）そうだ
（信）“そうだ”って お前…
Correct.
Correct?!
It's true that Lun Hu is a monster.
確かに輪虎はバケモノだ
But of course, he cannot break through a few hundred or a few thousand enemies on his own.
だが もちろん ヤツ１人で―
数百 数千の敵を
突破できるわけではない
We also must consider his soldiers that he always takes into battle.
（蒙恬）
輪虎の後ろには いつも必ず―
共に戦場をくぐり抜けてきた
輪虎兵の存在がある
It is because of those soldiers he leads that Lun Hu has his great ability to penetrate enemy lines.
その兵たちを率いてこその
輪虎の突破力だ
When Lun Hu fled his country, he took 700 elite soldiers with him to the State of Wei.
輪虎は 亡命するときに―
えりすぐった700人の兵を
魏国に連れてきた
それが この戦で輪虎の周りに控え
突撃の時を待っている
In this battle, they wait around Lun Hu and only attack when the time to charge occurs.
The Yuehua Unit will target and inter those 700 soldiers.
（蒙恬）楽華隊は
その700の兵たちを狙い撃ちし 葬る
Because then, it will no longer be realistically possible for Lun Hu to attack the Meng Ao headquarters.
そうすれば 現実的に―
輪虎が蒙驁本陣を討つことは
不可能になるからな
However, this is more of a preparatory move than anything.
（蒙恬）まあ でも これは―
布石の意味のほうが
大きいんだけどね
（信）布石？
Preparatory?
（王賁(おうほん)）そう簡単な話ではない
It's not that simple.
We, the Yufeng Unit fought with him on the first day.
（王賁）
初日に 玉鳳隊は ヤツらと戦ったが
個の力 集の力
どちらもヤツらのほうが上だった
And both their strength as individuals and in groups was greater than ours.
Lun Hu and his soldiers are
unstoppable once they start running.
走りだしたら
止められぬ輪虎と その兵を―
共に出向いて討つのが
ねらいだろうが
Say we're going to attack them together,
bearing that in mind, the ones to suffer the most damage from challenging them
それを差し引いても
ヤツらに挑んで 被害を受けるのは
would be the Yuehua Unit, Meng Tian.
楽華隊のほうだぞ 蒙恬
Why don't you call for a sortie, Lord Xin?!
（楚水）
なぜ出撃しないのですか？ 信どの
Was your plan not to fight together with the Yuehua Unit?!
楽華隊と共に戦うという
話ではなかったのですか？
At this rate, the Yuehua Unit will...
このままでは 楽華隊は…
（信）合図があるまで動くな！
Don't move until I give the signal!
This is part of Meng Tian's strategy, too.
これも蒙恬の作戦なんだ
（番陽(ばんよう)）賁さま
やはり楽華隊は苦戦しております
Lord Ben, it seems the Yuehua Unit truly is fighting a difficult battle.
この作戦は間違いだったのでは？
（王賁）いや そうは思わぬ
I believe this strategy could have been a mistake.
No, I don't think so.
In order to take down a major player like Lun Hu, some framework for an attack is necessary.
輪虎のような大物を討つには
攻めの組み立てが必要になる
（番陽）攻めの組み立て？
Framework for attack?
When attacking Lun Hu, you can be sure that the mighty Lun Hu soldiers will be a major barrier.
（王賁）輪虎を襲うとき―
必ず屈強な輪虎兵が
大きな障壁となって立ちはだかる
What Meng Tian is doing is trying to remove them beforehand.
（王賁）それを蒙恬は
先に取り除こうとしているのだ
Of course, that will be no easy task.
無論 容易なことではない
But he volunteered for this bloody first job.
だが…
（王賁）ヤツは自ら―
いちばん血を流す このつぶれ役を
買って出たんだ
（王賁）本当に 今回は
腹を決めているようだな 蒙恬
It looks like you've really resolved yourself this time, Meng Tian.
The Yuehua Unit is very capricious.
気分屋色の強い楽華隊だ
お前が前面でやる気を見せれば…
If you show outright enthusiasm...
the Yuehua Unit will be greatly excited
（王賁）楽華隊は大いに盛り上がり
and display far greater power than usual.
ふだん以上の力を発揮する
What's wrong, guys?!
どうした？ みんな
もう へばったのか？
Tired already?!
Like hell we are!
My soldiers are... being beaten?
僕の兵が やられてる？
H-Hold on a second!
（信）ちょ… ちょっと待て！
I don't get it, Meng Tian...
なんでだ？ 蒙恬
なんで自分が踏み台に…
犠牲になるようなマネするんだ？
Why would you sacrifice yourself for the rest of us...
and make yourself a stepping stone?!
You idiot. I don't intend to be some kind of self-sacrificing martyr.
（蒙恬）バカ！
自己犠牲の聖者のつもりはないぞ
ただ この重要な役回りは―
It's just that it's highly unlikely
今の玉鳳隊も 飛信隊も
こなせっこない
that this crucial job could be accomplished by the current Yufeng or Feixin Units.
It can only be done by the Yuehua Unit, so that's what we're going to do.
（蒙恬）やれるのは楽華隊だけ
だから やる
全ては―
This is all for the sake of defeating Lun Hu!
輪虎を討つために
By us three units!
俺たち３隊でな
Okay, now's a good time!
よし ころ合いだ！
That's...
（楚水）あれは…
So Wang Ben, Xin, I'm counting on you to take care of the rest!
（蒙恬）だから
王賁 信… その先は任せたぞ！
There's the signal, Lord Xin!
合図だ！ 信どの！
ンッ！ 行くぞ！ 飛信隊！
Let's go, Feixin Unit!
We're heading out, Yufeng Unit!
出るぞ 玉鳳隊！
Will the foot soldiers be all right back there?
（羌瘣(きょうかい)）
残していく歩兵は大丈夫なのか？
趣旨は什長(じゅうちょう)にまで伝達してある
それよりも 問題は―
I've informed the Shen Chiefs of our intentions.
The bigger question now...
is whether or not we can reach Lun Hu before the Yuehua Unit falls.
楽華隊が倒れる前に―
我々が輪虎のもとへ
たどりつけるかどうかだ
（兵士）
蒙恬さま！ かなり やられました
Lord Meng Tian!
We've had some considerable losses!
If we lose any more manpower, we may be completely routed!
これ以上 兵力を失うと
一気に 総崩れになります！
ああ　分かってる
Yeah, I know.
But the Lun Hu soldiers have been diminished just as much.
でも その分
輪虎兵も かなり減ったよ
Have all of my soldiers temporarily withdraw and gather together.
各所の僕の兵を
一度 下げて 集結させて
（圭）なっ… 将軍の兵をですか？
（輪虎）そう 急いで
Your soldiers, General!?
Yes, hurry!
Send in a fresh supply of Wei soldiers to fill in the gaps.
（輪虎）
下げた穴には 魏国軍の新手を投入
周りの包囲も固めて
１人も逃がさぬように
And be sure to tighten the encirclement, do not let a single person though.
Man, they got me.
まいったな
最初から僕の兵を狙ってくるとは
I never thought they'd be going for my soldiers to start with.
They're my precious arms and legs, but they're limited in their numbers.
数に限りのある
僕の貴重な手足だというのに
（信）オリャー！
Don't mind the small fries!
雑魚にかまうな！
適当にあしらって すっ飛ばせ！
Just do what you have to to get them out of your way!
ハッ… これは…
This is...
The enemy is visibly slow in reacting to us!
（楚水）我々に対して
敵の対応が目に見えて遅れている
隙間だ！ 隙間を駆け抜けるぞ！
There's opening!
We're gonna run through that opening!
We can do it! We might make it through!
いける！ いけるかもしれない！
At this rate, we can make up for starting late!
この調子なら
出遅れた分を取り戻せる！
（信）ああ 分かってる
Yeah, I know.
I told'ja, didn' I?
だから 言ったろう
全部 あいつの作戦どおりだって
This is all going according to that guy's plan!
Lun Hu
"We will make it in time because we started late", sir?
“出遅れたから間に合う”ですか？
そうだ
今回 楽華隊が突然 前に出たとき
That's right.
Earlier, when the Yuehua Unit suddenly came out early,
敵は
ほかの部隊の連動を警戒したはず
the enemy was most likely on the lookout for other units working with them.
だが 動いたのは楽華隊のみ
But the only ones that acted were the Yuehua Unit.
They acted alone and invaded the enemy headquarters without hesitation.
（王賁）ヤツらは
単独で躊躇(ちゅうちょ)なく敵本陣に突入し
And so the enemy's attention became focused on them.
敵の注意は ヤツらに向いた
The later we left,
俺たちが出るのが
遅ければ遅いほど―
敵の注意は 中で暴れる楽華隊に
集中するというわけだ
the more the enemy's attention would be concentrated on the Yuehua Unit which was among them.
Without those enemies as an obstacle,
騎馬隊に敵の障害さえなければ
our mounted units should be able to reach the exposed Lun Hu headquarters in no time.
前方に出てきている輪虎本陣までは
あっという間だ
It's the headquarters! Let's go!
（兵士）本陣だ！ いくぞ！
（鬨の声）
（じい）
蒙恬さま！ 飛信隊 玉鳳隊が―
Lord Meng Tian!
The Feixin Unit and Yufeng Unit are approaching!
近づきつつあります
（蒙恬）ああ
Okay!
Well then, I'll be leaving one last meager present.
それじゃ 最後にひとつ
ささやかな贈り物をしとくか
Left and right units! Retreat immediately!
左右の隊！ 一気に後退しろ！
ここも ゆっくり下がるぞ！
We're going to slowly retreat as well!
（兵士たち）オーッ！
（魏兵）逃げるぞ！
They're running!
After them! Don't let them get away!
（魏兵）追え 追え！ 逃がすな！
There's a path opening in front of us!
前に道ができた
L-Lord Ben, this is...!
（番陽）ほ… 賁さま これは…
It-It can't be...
（番陽）バ… バカな…
これも蒙恬の仕業なのか？
信じられぬ
This is Meng Tian's work as well? Unbelievable.
We managed to get this close to one of Lian Po's close aides?
廉頗の側近相手に
これほどの戦いをやってのけるとは
And what's more, these thee units that were so hostile before are suddenly acting together as allies.
しかも 反目し合っていた
この３隊のにわか連合軍を―
ひとつに まとめて…
いち早く千人将になった才能は
ダテではない
His sudden transition to a Thousand-Man General was not just for show.
No, Meng Tian's ability may already be beyond that of a Thousand-Man General!
いや 蒙恬の力は―
もはや 千人将の域すら
超えているかもしれぬ
A-Another unit is coming from the left! It looks to be about 300!
（輪虎兵）
ひ… 左より別の隊が迫ってます！
およそ300！
（圭）なに？
What?!
O-One is coming from the right as well!
（輪虎兵）み… 右からも来ます！
（圭）バカな！ いつの間に…
Impossible! When did they have the chance...?!
They've already made it very close, General!
（輪虎兵）既に
そこまで入ってきてます 将軍！
ハッ… 見ろ！
Look! It's the headquarters' flags!
本陣の旗だ！
輪虎は もう目の前だぞ！
Lun Hu is right in front of us now!
Lun Hu...!
輪虎…
（郭備(かくび)兵）輪虎…
Revenge for Lord Guo Bei!
郭備さまの敵！
Incoming, straight ahead!
正面 来るぞ！
What?!
なに？
Th-This is bad!
ハッ… マズイ
They caught us!
（信）捕まった！
Get out of our way!
（郭備兵）ジャマだ！ どけ！
What?! These guys are strong!
（信）何だ？ こいつら 強(つえ)え！
白ずくめの兵… こいつら まさか…
Soldiers clad in white...!
Could these ones be... Lun Hu's soldiers?!
（楚水）輪虎兵か
Kill them all!
（輪虎兵）皆殺しだ！
ンッ！
ここで輪虎兵が出てくるとは…
Lun Hu soldiers are appearing here?!
Weren't they fighting Meng Tian?!
こやつらは 蒙恬が
たたいたのではなかったのか？
（王賁）輪虎の周りを固めていた
最後の兵だろう
These are Lun Hu's final soldiers that form a shield around him.
He's unstintingly sent them to attack?! What a bold move...
（番陽）出し惜しみなく
繰り出してくるとは 大胆な…
つくづく攻め主体の姿勢のようだ
だが ここさえ抜ければ―
They have the posture of a core attack force.
But if we can just make it past them, there will be no major forces left to protect Lun Hu!
輪虎を守る猛者たちは もういない
この！
I told you...
ジャマだっつってんだろうが！
you're in our way!
Okay! Just a little!
しゃ！ もう少しだ！
C-Captain, behind us!
（兵士）た… 隊長！ 後ろが…
（信）うん？
The rest aren't keeping up at all!
後ろが全くついてきていません！
（信）なに？
What?!
何をしている 信どの！
What are you doing, Lord Xin?!
Keep going, push your way in!
そのまま突き進まれよ！
This is Lun Hu's final act of vain resistance!
（楚水）
これは輪虎の最後の悪あがきだ
You can break through!
信どのなら そのまま突破できる！
（楚水）アアッ！
（信）あっ 楚水！
Chu Shui!
Go, Lord Xin!
いけ！ 信どの！
Don't mind us, just take Lun Hu's head!
我らにかまわず
輪虎の首を取ってくだされ！
Chu Shui...
楚水…
Kill them!
（輪虎兵）殺せ！
（楚水）ウウッ！
Go, now!
（楚水）早く行け！
Chu Shui!
楚水！
I'll go back.
（羌瘣）私が戻ろう
（信）羌瘣…
Qiang Lei!
この先
まだ あの男は飛信隊に必要だ
The Feixin Unit... is going to need that man in the future.
Okay, I'm counting on you.
よし 頼んだぞ
I'm... going to take down Lun Hu!
俺は 輪虎を討つ！
The worst blow today
（輪虎）今回の最大の痛手は 僕の
私兵の大半を失ってしまったことだ
will be me losing the majority of my soldiers.
I'm going to have to come up with something when going into the major stages of the war.
これは 本番に向けて
何か考えないといけなくなった
But that's all.
（輪虎）だけど それだけだ
There won't be anything else major.
そのほかのことは…
別に大したことではない
Because being drawn on by enemies
（輪虎）敵に迫られたところで…
will not lead to my defeat.
僕が討たれることはないからね
Are you all right, Chu Shui?
無事か？ 楚水
（楚水）きょ… 羌瘣どの
L-Lord Qiang Lei!
Why did you come back?!
なぜ戻ったのだ？
（羌瘣）少し下がりながら戦うぞ
Let's fight while drawing back a bit.
Are you going to head back towards Lord Xin?!
信どののもとへ向かうのでは？
いや ここの輪虎兵を信の所へ
連れていくのは得策じゃない
No. It wouldn't be a good plan to bring the Lun Hu soldiers to where Xin is.
Let's leave Lun Hu's head... to them.
輪虎の首は あいつらに任せよう
（輪虎）おや？ 君は前に…
確か 飛信隊の…
Oh? You're that one from before. From the Feixin Unit I believe...
It's Xin.
信だ
We meet again, huh?
また会ってしまったね
I'm not letting you get away this time, Lun Hu.
今度は逃がさねえぞ 輪虎
（輪虎）ハハハッ… 逆だよ
今度は逃げてあげないよ
You've got it backwards.
I won't be letting you run this time.
（信）…んだと？ てめえ
What was that, bastard?!
そっちの槍使(やりつか)い君も含めて―
And including that spear user over there,
君たちは 相手の力量を
きちんと推し量れていない
you guys don't seem to have a firm grasp of your opponent's strength.
Did you think that between the two of you
２人がかりでなら この僕を
どうこうできるとでも思ったのかい
you might be able to somehow defeat me?
ざけんな てめえ！
Quit your bullshit, bastard!
チッ… こんなもんで！
You think this'll work?!
２人同時でもいいんだけど
少々 効率よくやらせてもらうよ
I wouldn't have a problem with both of them at once,
but I think I'll do this the more efficient way.
I'll leave that more manageable one for later.
くみしやすそうな君は後回し
I do believe the one I should be attacking first is...
やはり 先に たたいておくべきは…
Lord Wang Ben!
（兵士）王賁さま！
（兵士）ウオーッ！
（輪虎）ジャマ
You're in the way.
ハアッ！
（輪虎）よっと！
Woah there!
You're pretty full of spirit, but I think you're a bit dull because of your wound.
気迫は乗ってるが
ケガのせいで キレはイマイチかな
This bastard...
（王賁）こいつ…
Oh, that was fast.
へえ 速いな
Xin of the Feixin Unit,
（輪虎）飛信隊の信…
そこまで来たなら しかたない
if you've come that far, then I suppose I have no choice.
（王賁）狙っている…
He's changing targets?
では 君から
I'll start with you.
Stop, Xin!
止まれ！ し…
オリャー！
（はじけ飛ぶ音）
The one that doesn't know his opponent's strength is you, Lun Hu.
（信）力量を読めてねえのは
お前のほうだ 輪虎
誰が いちばん強えのか
きっちり教えてやるぜ！
I'll pound just who it is that's the strongest into that thick skull of yours!
（馬令）ええい
輪虎の本陣は どうなってる？
What's happening at Lun Hu's headquarters?!
Damn. I can't see a thing in all the dust that's kicking up!
（黄公）
ダメだ　乱戦の砂煙で見えぬ
It seems the Yuehua Unit has retreated,
（李充(りじゅう)）楽華隊は下がったようだが
代わりに入っていったのは
玉鳳隊と飛信隊か
but in their place, both the Yufeng and Feixin Units have entered?!
They're probably coordinating with the Yuehua Unit...
（馬令）楽華隊との連携だろうが
しかし
まさか３隊も身勝手に動くとは…
But I can't believe three units would act on their own!
（黄公）いかに独立遊軍とはいえ
成果なくば この責任は重大だぞ
Even if they are independent units,
if they don't produce results, they will bear a hefty responsibility!
（蒙驁）フォフォフォ…
それは当然のことじゃ
Well, of course.
しかし それは本人たちが いちばん
分かっていることじゃろうて
But those boys are the ones that know that best...
Wang Ben... Xin...
王賁… 信…
実戦向き…
Suited for combat...
The sort of human that can display greater power depending on his opponent's strength, eh?
相手の強さによって
より力を発揮しだす人間か
Well, everyone's like that, more or less.
まあ 誰でも 多かれ少なかれ
そういうものではあるけれど
この子の落差は すさまじく激しい
But the difference with this boy is incredible.
そして… この一撃の異常な重さ
And this abnormal weight of individual attacks...
おっとと…
Woah, there.
てめえ 王賁！
ジャマすんじゃねえ！
Hey, Wang Ben, don't interfere in my fight!
You're the one interfering!
ジャマは貴様だ
こいつは俺の獲物だ！
He is my prey!
Fuck off, you bastard!
（信）ざけんな てめえ！
Lord Lun Hu!
（輪虎兵）輪虎さま！
I-Is that man even human?!
（兵士）に… 人間か？ あの男
ンッ… ヘヘッ… さすがに強えな
I knew you were strong.
Looks like it's true that you actually landed a blow on General Wang Qi.
あの王騎(おうき)将軍に
ひと太刀浴びせたってのは―
ウソじゃなさそうだ
（輪虎）その辺のことは
茶化(ちゃか)してほしくないな
I'd prefer if you didn't make fun of things like that.
Well, I suppose you wouldn't have any idea what opposing General Wang Qi is like.
（輪虎）まあ…
王騎将軍を相手にすることが
どんなことか 分かるはずもないか
（信）フッ… ナメんな
Don't underestimate me.
…んなことは
俺たちだって分かってらぁ
I sure as hell know what that's like.
言っとくが
そいつは王騎将軍の一族だぜ
But just to let you know, that guy is part of Wang Qi's family.
Wang Qi's?
王騎の… では 君は？
So, then what about you?
俺か？
Me? I'm the man that inherited General Wang Qi's lance and his will from him!
俺は 王騎将軍から
矛と その遺志を受け継いだ男
And... I'm the man that will surpass those generals
（信）そして
その将軍たちをも超える―
and become the strongest Great General in history!
歴代最強の大将軍になる男だ！
オリャー！
Wang Qi's lance and will, eh?
王騎の矛と遺志か…
しかし “歴代最強の大将軍”とは
大きく出たねえ
But history's strongest Great General? That's quite a claim.
That means you're also going to surpass my lord, General Lian Po!
それじゃ 我が主(あるじ) 廉頗将軍も
超えるってことだ？
当たり前(めえ)だ！
Yer damn right!
After I slay you, I'm gonna kill Lian Po while I'm at it!
てめえを討ったあと ついでに
廉頗も ぶっ殺してやらぁ！
I do hope you don't get too full of yourselves.
（輪虎）
あんまり調子に乗らないでほしいな
Because both your lives are going to end today.
君たちの人生は
今日 ここで終わるんだから
Preview
A Wall That Must
be Overcome
End